现在我们重新回顾一下我们的最终细节框架
This is a good time to revisit
our final detail wireframe.
如果我们要在数据库中保存我们的天气预报信息
If we're going to store our weather
forecast information in a database
哪一些信息行是我们所需要的呢？
table, which columns
should our contract have?
在我们的数据库中，我们有天气预报的列表
In our database, we will have
a table of weather forecast entries.
我们用一行代表预测的某天
We use a row to represent
each forecast day.
并会把与预报相关的每一项数据保存在
And we'll store each piece of data
associated with the forecast in
一个单独的列中
a separate column.
看一下我们这个天气应用的界面，
which columns would we need for
哪一列才是我们的数据库表所需要的呢？
Taking a look at our weather UX,
the weather database table?
思考一下哪一列才是需要在数据库中被记录的
Think of which columns should
be in each database record.